ANTHONY CANGELOSI MBA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven and experienced in client relations, sales, marketing and event operations with a passion for creating and delivering world-class user experiences through brand integration. I am not in the sports business; I am in the business of helping other businesses by strategically thinking on their behalf to maximize client revenue through the vehicle of entertainment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

National Football League, Cleveland OH

July 2014 - Present

Manager of Corporate Partnership Activation, Cleveland Browns

- Manage and activate on book of multi-million dollar partnerships with the objective to grow the revenue from each partner
- Responsible for developing and presenting new business proposals to potential Cleveland Browns partners
- Manage new asset ideation sessions for partnership team, which includes media, hospitality, promotions, digital campaigns, etc.
- Quickly developing authentic business relationships with C-level clientele and day-to-day brand managers
- Take part in exploratory meetings, presentation of ideas, sales pitches and negotiation of terms with potential partners
- Collaborate internally with all departments to ensure partnership assets are achievable and understood
- Creation and management of an evolving partner website to help clients track deliverables and provide proof of performance in real time
- Utilize CRM systems and asset inventory systems to strategically maximize revenue

Major League Baseball, Sydney Australia

2012 - 2014

Commercial Director, Sydney Blue Sox

- Member of the implementation team for "Major League Baseball's Opening Series at the Sydney Cricket Ground" featuring the Los Angeles Dodgers and Arizona Cardinals
- Directed day-to-day operations of the Sydney Blue Sox with full responsibility for team budgets
 - Main business unit: Corporate partnership sales (strategy, sales, fulfillment and renewal process)
- Oversaw strategy and execution of ticket sales, merchandising, food/beverage, media platforms and fan engagement
- Managed the team relationship with the State Baseball Association, the baseball community, and government authorities
- Directed day-to-day operations of the ABL team, managing paid employees and volunteers
- Established and executed an annual business plan with aggressive targets specially in sponsorship

Sports Management Research Institute (SMRI), San Diego, CA

2011 - 2012

Operations/Fan Engagement Consultant

- Performed a league-wide study on behalf of the National Football League (NFL) focused on fan engagement and game day event service.
 - o The scope of the study included 200 guest service and sponsored fan engagement touch points per event
- Consulted with clients to analyze and improve overall event sponsor activation and fan experience
- Oversaw research plan, project management, data analysis and the development of overall recommendations to improve user experience
- Managed on-site, online and social media platforms for data collection
 - o Clients included: National Football League, U.S. Open (tennis), ATP/WTA, Oklahoma City Thunder & Red Bull

Major League Soccer, Los Angeles, CA

2009 - 2011

Account Executive, Chivas USA

- Planned, developed and implemented events to interact with and attract a regional and international fan base
- Developed proposals and marketing plans for potential clients with hospitality assets such as suites and premium ticketing experiences
- · Responsible for maintaining and growing an extensive portfolio of prospects and currents
- Top 2011 salesperson, grossing over \$100,000 in new sales for the soccer club breaking previous records held by Sr. executives

(MLS continued)

National MLS Sales Center, Blaine, MN

Trainee

- Participated in a comprehensive, two month training program emphasizing league best practices in ticket sales and sports marketing
- Sold tickets for multiple MLS teams, including Los Angeles Galaxy, FC Dallas, Real Salt Lake, and Colorado Rapids
 - o Completed program as the top revenue producer in the session

adidas, Herzogenaurach, Germany (adidas HQ)

2008

Consumer Marketing Internship

 Assisted senior executives with consumer segmentation, "go-to-market" research, global qualitative and quantitative reporting, competitor analysis reporting, focus group facilitation and market summaries for the sports performance and fashion business units

Hyatt Hotels Corporation, Orlando, FL

2002 - 2008

Various hotel positions including banquet serving and recreation

EDUCATION

University Of Findlay (ACBSP Accredited), Findlay, OH

2016

Masters of Business Administration, Concentrations: International Business and Organizational Leadership

Stetson University (ACBSP Accredited), Orlando, FL

2009

Bachelor of Business Administration, Majors: Marketing and Family Business

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Adapted Football League, Cleveland OH

Weekly Volunteer/Coach

- The Adapted Football League gives children and adults with more than 17 different types of disabilities the opportunity to participate in an organized and developmental sport that would otherwise be unavailable to them
- The primary focus for each player includes skill development, social interaction, and physical exercise